Russian agents, Iranian agents, freely operating in Venezuela, Hezbollah and Hamas.
This lady doesn't say everybody but the Decepticons and the Misfits is operating in Venezuela.
I'm surprised she didn't say young thug and YSL is down there too.
Look, this is very important. We don't want war. It was Maduro who started this war.
You are someone who stands for people's rights, for the rights of Venezuelans, for their democratic rights, for their human rights.
What about the rights to due process of the people who were on those boats?
I certainly defend the rights of everyone, not only Venezuelans.
That's why my voice has been, you know, loud all along this process. But you need to understand.
So typically when someone says but, anything that they said before that but is now null and void.
So this woman is about to explain, Jordi, I'm talking, why these people's rights on the boat are irrelevant and she's blaming it on somebody else.
And spoiler alert, it's not the administration who took their lives, a.k.a. the United States.
All the international community need to understand that this is a very cruel war.
It was Maduro who turned this into an international conflict.
Look, when you face...
Are those people expendable? That's really what I'm wondering. Are those people expendable on the boats?
It was Maduro who insisted on maintaining operations that have consequences.
So let's let this United States general explain to you why they're actually trying to do a regime change in Venezuela with the lady who looks like the joker being put in position.
Of course, the countries, Cuba, Venezuela and Nicaragua with Russia relationship.
So notice that a U.S. official and this lady from Venezuela have both said the same thing about Venezuela.
Russian agents, Iranian agents, freely operating in Venezuela.
That should be your key ding, ding, ding, that they're in cahoots.
Why this region matters with all of its rich resources and rare earth elements.
We've got the lithium triangle, which is needed for technology today.
Sixty percent of the world's lithium is in the lithium triangle.
I mean, she is like frothing at the mouth to get that lithium, honey.
Um, you have, uh, Venezuela's resources as well with, uh, with oil, uh, copper, gold.
We have the Amazon, uh, lungs of the world.
We have the 31% of the world's fresh water in this region too.
Um, I mean, it's just off the charts.
We have a lot to do.
This region matters.
It has a lot to do with national security and we need to step up our game.
The United States operates under the auspices that it deserves all the resources of the earth
in order to function and make the rich people of the United States richer, period.
And so you get people from other nations like Joker Lady who are like, well, I'm not in the United States,
but then if I rock with those rich people in the United States, I could be the rich people of Venezuela.
So we're the bystanders.
We're literally watching a war be started.
They, they cooked it up and now they serving it out.
This is what we call manufacturing consent.
When they create a boogeyman that they can place anywhere to legitimize their reasoning for going in and stealing resources.
And that lady right there, she's sending her people to slaughter.
It's maddening with all of this knowledge.
We know it.
We can't figure out how to stop it.
Look at my knee.
Maddening.
Head to AmandaSeals.com and get your tickets to the live stream performance and release of my new book.
What Would the Ancestors Say on November 8th.
Also check out When I'll Be in Your City with my book tour.
See you then.
Pop, pop.